const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'Which driver is currently a global brand ambassador with American company, Tommy Hilfiger?',
        answers: [
            'Michael Schumacher',
            'Lewis Hamilton',
            'Sebastian Vettel',
            'Niki Lauda'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Lewis Hamilton',
        explanation: 'Lewis Hamilton signed a global contract with Tommy Hilfiger as a brand ambassador and designer for the TOMMYXLEWIS line. Although F1 does not have a significant American following, this collaboration was a must-do for Tommy Hilfiger considering Lewis Hamilton\'s extreme international fame.',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which driver started his own airline?',
        answers: [
            'Michael Schumacher',
            'Lewis Hamilton',
            'Sebastian Vettel',
            'Niki Lauda'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Niki Lauda',
        explanation: 'As a native Austrian, Niki Lauda headquartered Lauda Air in Vienna. It later became a subsidiary of Austrian Airlines and is now no longer an airline, but is used for marketing purposes within Austrian Airlines.',
    },
    {
        question: 'The 2013 biographical film, <i>Rush</i>, starring Chris Hemsworth and Daniel Br√ºhl was inspired by the true story of the F1 rivalry between James Hunt and which driver?',
        answers: [
            'Michael Schumacher',
            'Lewis Hamilton',
            'Sebastian Vettel',
            'Niki Lauda'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Niki Lauda',
        explanation: 'The movie detailed one of the most infamous rivalries in F1, between James Hunt and Niki Lauda. Niki Lauda actually contributed to the film\'s accuracy and production details.',
    },
    {
        question: 'With five world championships, which driver is the current reigning world champion and is on track to win his sixth world championship in this 2019 season?',
        answers: [
            'Michael Schumacher',
            'Lewis Hamilton',
            'Sebastian Vettel',
            'Niki Lauda'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Lewis Hamilton',
        explanation: 'Lewis Hamilton and his teammate Valteri Bottas are respectively first and second place in the 2019 season. Due to their extreme dominance this season, it is predicted that Lewis Hamilton will take home another championship.',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which driver currently holds the most World Drivers\' Championships?',
        answers: [
            'Michael Schumacher',
            'Lewis Hamilton',
            'Sebastian Vettel',
            'Niki Lauda'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Michael Schumacher',
        explanation: 'Michael Schumacher has 7 World Drivers\' Championships. Tied for second-most is Lewis Hamilton and Juan Manuel Fangio with 5. Tied with third-most are Alain Prost and Sebastian Vettel with 4.',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which driver is the only one to have never driven on the Ferrari F1 racing team?',
        answers: [
            'Michael Schumacher',
            'Lewis Hamilton',
            'Sebastian Vettel',
            'Niki Lauda'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Lewis Hamilton',
        explanation: 'Lewis Hamilton started his career off in 2007 at McLaren, but has raced with Mercedes AMG since 2013 where he has won the World Drivers\' Championship in 4 out the last 5 years.',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which driver is nicknamed "Baby Schumi?"',
        answers: [
            'Michael Schumacher',
            'Lewis Hamilton',
            'Sebastian Vettel',
            'Niki Lauda'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Sebastian Vettel',
        explanation: 'Coming onto the F1 race scene in 2007 with such energy and promise, Vettel was dubbed "Baby Schumi" in reference to fellow German F1 champion, Michael Schumacher.',
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is currently a driver for Ferrari F1 racing team?',
        answers: [
            'Michael Schumacher',
            'Lewis Hamilton',
            'Sebastian Vettel',
            'Niki Lauda',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Sebastian Vettel',
        explanation: 'Sebastian Vettel has raced with Ferrari since 2015. Prior to Ferrari he raced for Toro Rosso and Red Bull.',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which driver was involved in a fiery crash and came close to death?',
        answers: [
            'Michael Schumacher',
            'Lewis Hamilton',
            'Sebastian Vettel',
            'Niki Lauda'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Niki Lauda',
        explanation: 'In 1976, Niki Lauda was involved in a nearly fatal crash on the Nurburgring in Germany. He was in the burning car for over one minute until fellow drivers were able to stop and pull him out of the burning car. He suffered severe burns, especially on his face, as well as lung damage due to inhaling the toxic fumes. "Healed enough", he returned on the racing scene after only six weeks. He finished the season in second-place, after rival James Hunt, who was only one point ahead of Lauda.',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which driver has a son who is currently racing one level below Formula 1, Formula 2?',
        answers: [
            'Michael Schumacher',
            'Lewis Hamilton',
            'Sebastian Vettel',
            'Niki Lauda'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Michael Schumacher',
        explanation: 'Mick Schumacher is Michael Schumacher\'s son and is expected to join the F1 scene within a few years, although the exact timeline of when is currently unknown.',
    }
];